<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_driver_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_controll_data">ControllDataActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pressure_data">PressureDataActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_driver_mode">DriverMode</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="activity_title_home">Offers</string>
    <string name="msg_no_notes">No Offer found!</string>
    <string name="lbl_new_note_title">New Note</string>
    <string name="lbl_edit_note_title">Edit Note</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_note">Enter your note!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_offers">OffersActivity</string>


    <string name="VinCommand">Vehicle Identification Number (VIN)</string>

    <string name="ModuleVoltageCommand">Control module voltage is the voltage supplied to the ECU.\n
  It isn\'t battery voltage but is usually close enough when the vehicle is running.\n
 </string>

    <string name="TimingAdvanceCommand">Timing Advance
    It refers to the spark igniting the air-fuel mixture in the cylinder in relation
      to the piston position in crankshaft degrees.\n The timing of the spark must change
      with engine conditions for the engine to run efficiently.\n
     </string>

    <string name="EquivalentRatioCommand">

  Fuel systems that use conventional oxygen sensor display the commanded open
  loop equivalence ratio while the system is in open loop.\n
  Should report 100% when in closed loop fuel.\n
  To obtain the actual air/fuel ratio being commanded, \n multiply the
  stoichiometric A/F ratio by the equivalence ratio.\n For example, gasoline
  stoichiometric is 14.64:1 ratio.\n If the fuel control system was commande an
  equivalence ratio of 0.95,\n the commanded A/F ratio to the engine would be
  14.64 * 0.95 = 13.9 A/F.\n

    </string>

    <string name="DistanceMILOnCommand"> Distance traveled with malfunction indicator lamp (MIL) on
</string>

    <string name="TimeRunWithMILOnCommand">Time Run With malfunction indicator lamp (MIL)On</string>

    <string name="DistanceSinceCCCommand">  Distance traveled since trouble codes cleared-up.\n
</string>

    <string name="TimeSinceTroubleCodesClearedCommand">TimeSince Trouble Codes Cleared-up\n</string>

    <string name="AbsoluteLoadCommand">
    Absolute Engine load value.\n
     it relies on the flow of air and basically engine displacement.\n
        it Ranges from 0 to approximately 0.95 for naturally aspirated engines, 0 – 4 for boosted engines.\n

 </string>

    <string name="LoadCommand">  Calculated Engine Load value.\n

  There isn\'t a single sensor it uses to figure this out.\n For a gasoline (or spark ignition) engine,
  it utilizes the Air Intake Sensor (IAT), Manifold Absolute Pressure (MAP)
  sensor, Throttle Position Sensor (TPS), and Engine Coolant Temperature (ECT) sensor
  to do calculations.\n

 </string>
    <string name="MassAirFlowCommand"> Mass Air Flow (MAF)
 
  (MAF) is a sensor used to determine the mass flow rate of air entering a fuel-injected internal combustion engine.\n
  The air mass information is necessary for the engine control unit (ECU)
  to balance and deliver the correct fuel mass to the engine.\n Air changes its density with temperature
  and pressure.\n </string>

    <string name="OilTempCommand">  Displays the current engine Oil temperature.\n</string>

    <string name="RelativeAcceleratorPedalPositionCommand">Relative Accelerator PedalPosition.\n
    The accelerator position information is transferred to the throttle
        actuator control (TAC) module and the powertrain control module (PCM).\n
     The driver pressing down on the accelerator pedal, the pressure on the pedal rotates
        the throttle plate inside the throttle body, which opens a passage inside this unit
        to allow for the passage of airflow.\n
        As the air travels through the throttle passage to the intake manifold, it activates airflow
        sensors that manipulates the engine control unit and forces fuel into the fluid injector system.</string>

    <string name="FuelInjectionTimingCommand"> injection timing is the time at which injection of fuel into the
        combustion chamber begins.\n
        It is usually expressed in crank angle degrees (CAD) relative to TDC of the compression stroke.</string>


    <string name="RPMCommand">  Displays the current engine revolutions per minute (RPM).\n</string>


    <string name="RuntimeCommand">  Engine runtime since engine start </string>

    <string name="ThrottlePositionCommand"> Read the throttle position in percentage.\n
  what is a throttle ?\n
  a device controlling the flow of fuel or power to an engine.\n
</string>


    <string name="AirFuelRatioCommand">Air–fuel ratio (AFR) is the mass ratio of air to a gaseous fuel present in a combustion process.\n
    If exactly enough air is provided to completely burn all of the fuel, the ratio is known as the stoichiometric mixture.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ConsumptionRateCommand">Fuel Consumption Rate per hour.</string>

    <string name="FindFuelTypeCommand">  Determine the vehicle fuel type.\n</string>

    <string name="FuelLevelCommand">  Current fuel level in percentage.</string>

    <string name="FuelTrimCommand"> fuel trims are the percentage of change in fuel over time.\n
  For the engine to operate properly, the air:fuel ratio needs to stay within a small window of 14.7:1.\n

 If the o2 sensors inform the engine computer that the exhaust mixture is lean, the
  computer adds fuel by lengthening injector pulse, or "on-time", to compensate.\n
  Conversely, if the o2 sensors inform the computer that the exhaust is rich,
  the computer shortens injector pulse, adding less fuel to compensate in order to bring
  the rich condition down.\n
 
   Changes in o2 sensor voltages causs a direct change in fuel.\n
   The short term fuel trim (STFT) refers to immediate changes in fuel occurring
  several times per second.\n The long term fuel trims (LTFT) are driven by the short term fuel trims.\n
  LTFT refers to changes in STFT but averaged over a longer period of time.\n
  A negative fuel trim percentage indicates a taking away of fuel while a
  positive percentage indicates an adding of fuel.\n
    while negative value indicates the engine computer is subtracting fuel. </string>

    <string name="WidebandAirFuelRatioCommand"> Oxygen sensors are usually located in the exhaust manifolds or exhaust piping.\n
  They read data from the exhaust gasses leaving the engine.\n
  This is helpful in determining if the engine is running correctly.\n
  However, if you are trying to determine the AirFuelRatio entering the engine,
  which is what it sounds like, the oxygen sensors would not be very helpful.\n
  A very high or very low reading could indicate that the intake AFR is not correct,
  but getting an actual number would be difficult.\n
 </string>


    <string name="BarometricPressureCommand">
  The barometric (BARO) sensor is used by the engine control module (ECM)
  to measure the pressure of the atmosphere.\n The pressure is affected
  by weather conditions, air volume, and altitude.\n
 </string>


    <string name="FuelPressureCommand">
        the low pressure pump pressure.\n
        ranges from 0 to 765 kpa.\n
        On a car with fuel injection there can be two fuel pumps,
  one high-pressure and one low-pressure.\n
  The low-pressure pump moves the gas from the tank up to the
  high pressure pump.\n The high pressure pump then raises the pressure to a
  level that will be useful to the injectors.\n
  These pressures are all controlled by regulators so that any of these PIDs should be fairly
  constant and not affected by load in a well running engine.\n
  Low fuel pressure would be the result of failure or clog in the fuel system.\n
 </string>

    <string name="FuelRailPressureCommand">
         the pressures in direct gas injection, high pressuer pump pressure.\n
        ranges from 0 to 655,350 kpa
   On a car with fuel injection there can be two fuel pumps,
  one high-pressure and one low-pressure.\n
  The low-pressure pump moves the gas from the tank up to the
  high pressure pump.\n The high pressure pump then raises the pressure to a
  level that will be useful to the injectors.\n
  These pressures are all controlled by regulators so that any of these PIDs should be fairly
  constant and not affected by load in a well running engine.\n
  Low fuel pressure would be the result of failure or clog in the fuel system.\n
 </string>

    <string name="IntakeManifoldPressureCommand">
        The Manifold Absolute Pressure (MAP) sensor is a key sensor because it senses engine load.\n
  The sensor generates a signal that is proportional to the amount of vacuum in the intake manifold.\n
  The engine computer then uses this information to adjust ignition timing and fuel enrichment.\n
 
  When the engine is working hard, intake vacuum drops as the throttle opens wide.\n
  The engine sucks in more air, which requires more fuel to keep the air/fuel ratio in balance.\n
  In fact, when the computer reads a heavy load signal from the MAP sensor,
  it usually makes the fuel mixture go slightly richer than normal so the engine can produce more power.\n

  When conditions change and the vehicle is cruising along under light load, coasting or decelerating,
  less power is needed from the engine.\n The throttle is not open very wide or may be closed causing
  intake vacuum to increase.\n The MAP sensor senses this and the computer responds by leaning out the
  fuel mixture to reduce fuel consumption.\n
 </string>

    <string name="AirIntakeTemperatureCommand">The Intake Air Temperature sensor (IAT) monitors the temperature
  of the air entering the engine.\n The engine computer (PCM) needs this information to estimate
  air density so it can balance  air/fuel mixture.\n Colder air is more dense than hot air,
  so cold air requires more fuel to maintain the same air/fuel ratio.\n The PCM changes the air/fuel ratio
  by changing the length (on time) of the injector pulses.\n
 </string>


    <string name="AbsoluteEvapSystemVaporPressureCommand">
        The EVAP system is a fully closed system designed to maintain stable fuel tank pressures without
        allowing fuel vapors to escape to the atmosphere.\n
        Fuel vapor is normally created in the fuel tank as a result of evaporation.
    </string>

    <string name="EvapSystemVaporPressureCommand">
        The EVAP system is a fully closed system designed to maintain stable fuel tank pressures without
        allowing fuel vapors to escape to the atmosphere.\n
        Fuel vapor is normally created in the fuel tank as a result of evaporation.
    </string>


    <string name="AmbientAirTemperatureCommand">
  Ambient Air temperature is used to modify air
  conditioning system operation and display outside air temperature.\n
 </string>
    <string name="CatalystTemperatureCommand">
    A catalytic converter is an exhaust emission control device that converts toxic gases and pollutants
        in exhaust gas into less-toxic pollutants by catalyzing a redox reaction (an oxidation and a reduction reaction).\n

        Catalytic converter efficiency and temperature go hand and hand. If the
		converter is working as it should, the outlet temperature should be
		slightly higher than the inlet.\n
        usually two sensors will be fitted,
        with one before the catalyst and one after to monitor the temperature rise
        over the catalytic-converter core.\n

</string>

    <string name="EngineCoolantTemperatureCommand">
  Engine Coolant Temperature Sensor is a sensor that determine the temperature of the engine coolant.\n
  Normal range from 90 to 104.\n
  more than 104 please check your coolant level.\n
  less than 85 means engine is warming up.\n
    </string>

    <string name="SpeedCommand"> Current speed.\n
</string>

    <string name="ActualEnginePercentTorqueCommand">the calculated output torque of the engine.\n Power=torque X RPM </string>
    <string name="EngineReferenceTorqueCommand"> display the engine reference torque value. This value does not change.</string>

    <string name="EGRErrorCommand">Calculated error as percent of actual commanded EGR.\n
        Negative percent is less than commanded and positive is more than commanded.\n
        The greater the value, the more likely the EGR valve is sticking.</string>
    <string name="CommandedEGRCommand"> exhaust gas recirculation (EGR) is a nitrogen oxide (NOx) emissions reduction technique.\n
     a primary benefit of external EGR valves on a spark ignition engine is an increase in efficiency.\n
    Thepercentage vlue between 0% and 100% where the EGR solenoid is duty cycled on and off by the PCM
        (depending on vehicle speed, engine load and temperature).</string>

    <string name="CommandedEvaporativePurgeCommand">
        This value should read 0% when no purge is commanded
        and 100% at the maximum commanded purge position flow.\n
        The purge valve is the part of the vehicle Evaporative Emission Control (EVAP) system.\n
        The EVAP system prevents fuel vapors in the fuel tank from escaping into the atmosphere.
        The EVAP system traps fuel vapors from the fuel tank and temporarily stores them in the charcoal canister.
        When the engine is running under certain conditions, the fuel vapors are purged from the
        canister and burned inside the engine.\n
    </string>

    <string name="EthanolPercentageCommand">Ethanol fuel percentage.  </string>
    <string name="HybridBatteryPackRemainingLifeCommand">Hybrid Battery Pack Remaining Life.</string>

    <string name="DriverDemandEnginePercentTorqueCommand">The driver torque represents the torque requested by the driver as
        a function of engine speed and accelerator pedal position.\n </string>

    <!--
    <string name="DtcNumberCommand"> This command will for now read MIL (check engine light) state and number of
  diagnostic trouble codes currently flagged in the ECU.\n
  Perhaps in the future we\'ll extend this to read the 3rd, 4th and 5th bytes of
  the response in order to store information about the availability and
  completeness of certain on-board tests.\n</string>
    -->

    <string name="PendingTroubleCodesCommand">what is pending DTCs ??\n
        Pending codes are caused by intermittent faults or faults that the PCM needs to see happen
        in two consecutive warm-up cycles to set the code.\n
        If the fault does not reappear within 40 warm-up cycles, the code will be cleared from memory.\n
        If the fault reappears for the specified number of times, the code will then mature into
        a diagnostic trouble code (DTC) and the PCM will command the check engine light to illuminate.\n \n
        </string>

    <string name="PermanentTroubleCodesCommand">
        what is Permanent DTCs??\n
        These are codes only the computer can clear.\n Even if you’ve made
      a successful repair , these codes will
        remain in memory until the computer has completed its own system test.\n
    In most cases, Permanent DTCs will erase when the customer drives the vehicle in his or
        her normal daily use if the repair has already been successfully completed.\n\n
</string>

    <string name="TroubleCodesCommand"> Diagnostic Trouble Codes or OBD2 Trouble Codes are codes that
        the car’s OBD system uses to notify you about an issue.\n
        Each code corresponds to a fault detected in the car. When the vehicle detects an issue, it will activate the corresponding
        trouble code.\n\n </string>


    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="termsOfService">Do you agree to share your car own data with us ??\n</string>

</resources>
